1.What are the six combinations of access modifier keywords and what do they do?

public  --> accessible everywhere 
protect internal --> accessible everywhere except non-derived class from different assembly
protect --> accessible in the same class or derived class
internal --> accessible in the same assembly
private protect --> accessible within class and derived class from same assembly
private --> accessible only within class

2.What is the difference between the static, const, and readonly keywords when applied to a type member?

Constant and ReadOnly keyword is used to make a field constant which value cannot be modified. 

Constant fields or local variables must be assigned a value at the time of declaration and after that, they cannot be modified.

Readonly field can be initialized either at the time of declaration or within the constructor of the same class

The static keyword is used to make members static that can be shared by all the class objects

3. What does a constructor do?
It's used to create an object of class and initialize class members
 
4. Why is the partial keyword useful?
Partial key is used to split the definition of a class, a struct, an interface or a method over two or more source files.

When working on large projects, spreading a class over separate files enables multiple programmers to work on it at the same time.

Code can be added to the class without having to recreate the source file.

5. What is a tuple?
A data structure which may consist of multiple parts.
A tuple allows you to combine multiple values of possibly different types into a single object
C# tuple is a data structure that provides an easy way to represent a single set of data.

6. What does the C# record keyword do?
A new reference type in C# 9 that you can create instead of classes or structs.
It is a lightweight, immutable data type with primarily read-only properties.
A record has the main purpose of storing data

7. What does overloading and overriding mean?
Overloading means there are multiple methods with the same name but different parameters within a class. Which provides reusability and different functionality of a method.

Overriding allows the derived class to provide a specific implementation of a method that is already provided by the parent class.

8. What is the difference between a field and a property?
A field is a variable of any type that is declared directly in a class.
A Property is a member that provides mechanism to read and write or compute of a private field.
Properties provide a level of abstraction allowing you to change the fields while not affecting the external way they are accessed by the things that use your class

9. How do you make a method parameter optional?
There are different ways to make parameter optional. 
First, use parameters arrays --> allow you to pass any number of parameters to the method
Second, use default parameters --> We can make a parameter optional by assigning default values for that parameter
Third, use optional attribute --> [Optional]
Last, use method overloading 

10. What is an interface and how is it different from abstract class?
An Interface is a contract gives a lists of methods that have to be implemented.

The difference between interface and abstract class:
First, interface can only have method declaration not implementation while abstract class can have concrete method in it.
Second, interface support multiple inheritance but abstract class can not
Third, interface can not have constructor while abstract class can
Forth, interface should be fully implemented.
Fifth, interface contains only public access modifier while abstract class can have different kinds of access modifier
Sixth, interface does not contain static members while abstract class does


11. What accessibility level are members of an interface?
Public

12. True/False. Polymorphism allows derived classes to provide different implementations
of the same method.
True

13. True/False. The override keyword is used to indicate that a method in a derived class is
providing its own implementation of a method.
False

14. True/False. The new keyword is used to indicate that a method in a derived class is
providing its own implementation of a method.
True

15. True/False. Abstract methods can be used in a normal (non-abstract) class. 
False

16. True/False. Normal (non-abstract) methods can be used in an abstract class. 
True

17. True/False. Derived classes can override methods that were virtual in the base class. 
True

18. True/False. Derived classes can override methods that were abstract in the base class.
True

19. True/False. In a derived class, you can override a method that was neither virtual non abstract in the base class.
False

20. True/False. A class that implements an interface does not have to provide an
implementation for all of the members of the interface.
False, it has to provide all the implementation of the interface

21. True/False. A class that implements an interface is allowed to have other members that
aren’t defined in the interface.
True

22. True/False. A class can have more than one base class.
False

23. True/False. A class can implement more than one interface.
True

24. What is meant by the terms managed resource and unmanaged resource in .NET
Managed objects are created, managed and under scope of CLR. 
Unmanaged objects are usually used to describe something not directly under the control of the garbage collector

24. What's the purpose of Garbage Collector in .NET?
Manages the allocation and release of memory for your application.
