1. Describe the problem generics address.

Generics increase the reusability of the code. You don't need to write code to handle different data types. It helps to reuse the code without replicating type-specific code.
Generic is type safe

2. How would you create a list of strings, using the generic List class?

List<string> strList = new List<string>();

3. How many generic type parameters does the Dictionary class have?

There are two generic type parameters in Dictionary class (TKey, TValue)

4. True/False. When a generic class has multiple type parameters, they must all match.
True

5. What method is used to add items to a List object?

Add()

6. Name two methods that cause items to be removed from a List.

RemoveAt() --> remove item at a particular index
Remove() --> remove item if exist in the list

7. How do you indicate that a class has a generic type parameter?

You specify a type parameter in an angle brackets after the class name. For example List<T> where T is a type parameter

8. True/False. Generic classes can only have one generic type parameter.
False

9. True/False. Generic type constraints limit what can be used for the generic type.
True

10. True/False. Constraints let you use the methods of the thing you are constraining to.
True
