1. What type would you choose for the following "numbers"?
A person's telephone number string
A person's height float
A person's age short
A person's gender (Male, Female, Prefer Not To Answer) string
A person's salary decimal
A book's ISBN string
A book's price decimal
A book's shipping weight float
A country's population int or long
The number of stars in the universe long
The number of employees in each of the small or medium businesses in the
United Kingdom (up to about 50,000 employees per business) int

2. What are the difference between value type and reference type variables?

Value type directly contain their data and Reference type store the reference(address) of the data


3. What happens when you divide an int variable by 0?
It will throw DivideByZeroException

4. What happens when you divide a double variable by 0?
Dividing a floating-point value by zero doesn't throw an exception; it results in positive infinity, negative infinity, or not a number (NaN), according to the rules of IEEE 754 arithmetic.

5. What happens when you overflow an int variable, that is, set it to a value beyond its
range?
When you overflow the int variable, it will loop back to the negative side

6. What is the difference between x = y++; and x = ++y;?
y++ is using postfix increment operator, ++y is using prefix increment operator
In y++ the value of variable is printed first then it is incremented whereas in ++y the value is incremented first and then it is displayed.

7. What is the difference between break, continue, and return when used inside a loop
statement?

When using break inside the loop, it will immediately jump outside the loop and execute the code after the loop
When using continue inside the loop, it will skip the rest of the code after continue inside loop and jump to the next iteration
When using return inside the loop, it will immediately return the function, no matter if there is code after the loop or not.

8. What are the three parts of a for statement and which of them are required?
The three parts of a for statement are initializer, condition, iterator 
The initializer initialize the variable we want to start in a loop
The condition check the loop condition for each loop cycle
The iterator change the loop variable after each loop

All three parts are optional, you can initialize the variable before loop, and condition and iterator can be defined inside the code block.
